revisitors.com 2017-06-06

# Targeted Traffic | Website Traffic | Buy Web Traffic

Your browser has Javascript disabled. Please enable your Javascript support to enjoy all Revisitors.com features 

Effective on July 13, 2010 

This privacy statement describes how Revisitors Srl collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [www.revisitors.com ](https://www.revisitors.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you 

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number 
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address 
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password 
  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences 

We also collect the following information from you 

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type 

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. 

We use this information to 

  * Fulfill your order 
  * Send you an order confirmation 
  * Send you requested product or service information 
  * Respond to customer service requests 
  * Send you a newsletter 
  * Send you marketing communications 
  * Respond to your questions and concerns 
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts 
  * Conduct research and analysis 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [steve@revisitors.com ](mailto:steve@revisitors.com). 

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

We may also disclose your personal information 

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, 
  * if Revisitors Srl is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

_PayPal_

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site. 

_Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider_

Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose. 

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site. 

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used. 

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Revisitors Srl. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

## Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [steve@revisitors.com ](mailto:steve@revisitors.com)

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [steve@revisitors.com](mailto:steve@revisitors.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Additional Policy Information

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [steve@revisitors.com ](mailto:steve@revisitors.com). 

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below: 

Revisitors Srl 

Via Giacinta Pezzana 63 

Rome, Lazio, Italy00197

By using Revisitors.com you agree to our use of cookies to enhance your experience.[Learn more](https://www.revisitors.com/privacypolicy.html)
